http://www.cmhouston.org/privacy-policy

Support UsMembershipLog InLog OutInformationFiddle Sticks ToysFind great, educator-approved toys and games that inspire learning!Shop NowTemporary ClosureAdmissionDirections and ParkingFiddle Sticks Online ShopGroups and Field ExperiencesBirthday PartiesHost an EventFAQAll-Time AccessAll-Time AccessWe’re taking connectivity to the next level with you and your family in mind.Join for FreeMy ProfileJoin All-Time Access3D Virtual Field Trips3D Virtual Field TripsThe Daily BroadcastGeek Out LiveMyProjects LiveEpic Adventure Pop UpComing SoonMr. O on InventingComing SoonEvents CalendarExhibitsChallenge CourseCyberchaseEcoStationEveryday PeopleFlowWorksGenius StationHeart and SeoulHow Does It Work?Invention ConventionInventor’s WorkshopKids’ HallKidtropolisMaker AnnexMatter FactoryParent Resource LibraryPower Science LabPowerPlaySECRET Spy GameSights UnseenTot*SpotTake a 3D Virtual Field TripExperience our exhibits from anywhere, anytime!Join All-Time AccessEducatorsCommunityRead Strong All Year LongIt’s time to get all children hooked on books!Learn MoreOutreach ProgramsGet InvolvedInformationTemporary ClosureAdmissionDirections and ParkingFiddle Sticks Online ShopGroups and Field ExperiencesBirthday PartiesHost an EventFAQAll-Time Access3D Virtual Field Trips3D Virtual Field TripsThe Daily BroadcastGeek Out LiveMyProjects LiveEvent CalendarExhibitsEducatorsCommunityCommunity ImpactOutreach ProgramsGet InvolvedSupport UsMembershipLog InLog OutMy ProfileBuy TicketsChildren’s Museum HoustonPrivacy PolicyOur Privacy StatementChildren’s Museum Houston is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Web sites. This policy may change without prior notice. Some web pages created by Children’s Museum Houston use cookies, which are small text files that may be placed on your hard disk for record-keeping purposes. It is essentially your identification card, and cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. It is uniquely yours and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. A cookie’s purpose is to tell the server that you returned to that Web page. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. Furthermore, a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer. The use of cookies is an industry standard. Many major websites use cookies to provide useful features for their customers. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you’d prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you will not be able to take full advantage of a website if you do so.Children’s Museum Houston will not send you any unsolicited information, including email regarding any commercial offers or advertisements at any time. We value the relationships we have with our customers and future customers, so we respect these concerns.Linked sites are not under the control of the Children’s Museum of Houston. Therefore, Children’s Museum Houston is not responsible or liable for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site. Links are provided to you as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply the endorsement of the site by Children’s Museum Houston.Donor Privacy PolicyChildren’s Museum Houston respects your privacy. We protect your personal contact information and adhere to all legislative requirements with respect to protecting privacy.We do not rent, sell, trade or otherwise share our donor mailing lists. The information you provide will be used to deliver services and keep you informed and up to date on the activities of Children’s Museum Houston, including programs, services, special events, funding needs, opportunities to give or volunteer, or other periodic contacts.You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. If at any time you wish to be removed from any of these contacts, please contact us by phone at (713) 522-1138 or email us and we will gladly accommodate your request.Mark Your CalendarExplore Events Calendar
Dec 10, 2020
Dec 10, 2020
Dec10—Dec10Dec10Free Drive-Up VaccinationsQualifying families will be offered free vaccinations every second Thursday of the month thru May 2021.Event Details
Dec 11, 2020
Dec 30, 2020
Dec11—Dec30Dec11Chevron Maker Annex Virtual WorkshopsSee what our Maker Annex engineers have in store for you during these at-home workshops.Event DetailsFind Out FirstSign up for e-news and be the first to know about special events, discounts and more!I’m Interested InMuseum NewsVirtual Learning and All-Time AccessEducator-Approved Toys and GamesWays to Get InvolvedI’m a ParentI’m an EducatorYou’re all signed up!Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.
English
Spanish
A Playground for Your Mind™Children’s Museum Houston1500 Binz St, Houston, TX 77004(713) 522-1138Children’s Museum Houston is a501(c)(3) organization.About UsAccessibilityCareers and InternshipsContact UsDonation RequestFAQFiddle Sticks Online ShopFort Bend Children’s Discovery CenterGift CardsNewsPrivacy PolicyDesigned and Built by Poetic.Children’s Museum Houston is a registered 501(c)(3) organization.Designed and Built by Poetic.
